Democracy isn't a spectator sport.
Boys State is a documentary film directed by Jesse Moss.
This raucous journey into the heart of democracy captures an unusual rite of passage: 1,100 teenage boys
from across Texas coming together to build a representative government from the ground up.
Self, played by Ben Feinstein.
Self, played by Steven Garza.
Self, played by Robert MacDougall.
Self, played by René Otero.
Self, played by Eddy Proietti Conti.
Boys State is a 2020 American documentary film directed and
produced by Jesse Moss and Amanda McBaine.
It follows a thousand teenage boys attending Boys State in Texas, coming
to build a representative government from the ground up.
The film had its world premiere at the Sundance Film Festival
on January 24, 2020, where it won the U.S.
Documentary Competition Grand Jury Prize.
It was released on Apple TV+ on August 14, 2020, by A24 and Apple.
In 2024, Jesse Moss and Amanda McBaine released the companion film Girls
State, which follows the 2022 Girls State Program in Missouri.